Tech Lead WILSON WU

wilson96wu@gmail.com

+27 725716932



https://wilson96wu.github.io/cv/

EXPERIENCE

Company A

Developer | since January 2016

Programming and watching cute cat videos.

Company B

Frontend Developer | January 2015 - December 2015

Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

Company C

Trainee | March 2014 - December 2014

Making coffee and baking cookies.

EDUCATION

Major in Hacking and Computer Penetration, University A, New York, USA.

Master of Arts | March 2012 - December 2013

Major in Engineering, University B, Los Angeles, USA.

Bachelor of Science | March 2009 - December 2011

SKILLS

Specializing in Game Engine development. Proficient in software architecure design. Fluent in English and Chinese.

- JavaScript/TypeScript
- HTML5
- CSS3

- Node.js
- Vue
- C#/C++

SQL

About me

I am currently working as a Senior Developer Level 2/Tech Lead in the Gaming Industry. I gained my master's degree in computer science in 2007. Worked as full stack developer from 2007 to 2009 by building intelligent building management systems with C++ and SQL. In 2009, I joined the gaming industry, became a front-end developer working on C++, ActionScript, JavaScript, and typescript. I created my first